CARLOS GERMÁN JOFRÉ

Full Stack Developer

Location: Buenos Aires, Argentina
jof.uncuyo@gmail.com
Phone: +54 9 11 2792 5467
Github: github.com/whoknowsi
LinkedIn: /in/carlos-jofre-830273210/
Portfolio: whoknows-portfolio.netlify.app

I am a computer science student at the University of Buenos Aires and a Full Stack Web Developer. I have a solid foundation in programming languages and I have worked on various web development projects using multiple libraries and frameworks.

Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- React
- React Native
- Next.js
- Vue.js
- Node.js
- Express.js
- MongoDB
- MySQL / MariaDB
- Firebase / Google Cloud
- Tailwind / Bootstrap
- Git
- Jest / Cypress / Playwright

Experience

Freelance web developer

Jan 2023 - Mar 2023

Currently working on ServicioLibre web app:

- Collaborating with a team to develop a service application that connects consumers with service providers.
- Designing and implementing key features of the application, ensuring they meet user needs and are scalable for future growth.
- Troubleshooting and resolving technical issues to ensure a seamless user experience.

Web developer

Jul 2022 - Oct 2022

Responsibilities:

- Developed a virtual 360 tour using Three.js and WebGL.
- Added interactive hotspots to the tour for user engagement.
- Optimized loading and smooth navigation implementing a tile-based system that dynamically loads and renders the necessary tiles based on the user's position and zoom level.

Frontend developer

Feb 2022 - Jun 2022

Responsibilities:

- Contributed to the development and maintenance of a visually appealing and user-friendly website for MaridajeClub's live product sales platform.
- Implemented the live video streaming system to enable customers to watch product demonstrations and make informed purchasing decisions.
- Collaborated with the frontend team to ensure efficient and effective development and deployment of new features and improvements to the platform.

Education

Bachelor of Computer Science

University of Buenos Aires

2021 - Present

Licenses & Certifications

Full Stack Open - University of Helsinki

Nov 2022

https://studies.cs.helsinki.fi/stats/api/certificate/fullstackopen/en/867a851012773dbe7db3d5d71c333a8a1dbe7db3d5d71c33a8a1dbe7db3d5d71c33a8a1dbe7db3d5d71c33a8a1dbe7db3d5d71c33a8a1dbe7db3d5d71c33a8a1dbe7db3d5d71c33a8a1dbe7db3d5d71c33a8a1dbe7db3d5d71c33a8a1dbe7db3d5d71c33a8a1dbe7db3d5d71c33a8a1dbe7db3d5d71c33a8a1dbe7db3d5d71c33a8a1dbe7db3d5d71c33a8a1dbe7db3d5d71c33a8a1dbe7db3d71c33a8a1dbe7db3d71c33a8a1dbe7db3d71c3a8a1dbe7db4d71c3a8a1dbe7db4d71c3a8a1dbe7db4d71c3a8a1dbe7db4d71c3a8a1dbe7db4d71c3a8a1dbe7db4d71c3a8a1dbe7db4d71c3a8a1dbe7db4d71c3a8a1dbe7db4d71c3a8a1dbe7db4d71c3a8a1d

C1 Advanced - EF SET https://www.efset.org/cert/KR1a48

Jan 2023

Languages

• Spanish: Native

• English: C1 Advanced